Wealth. Fame. Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for!
One piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary?
Until someone proves it real.
Through it all!
Through all the trouble and times!
Through the heartache
and through the pain!
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend?
We are, we are on a cruise!
We are.
I don't care how much of
a badass he used to be!
Now he's just a cook.
I wouldn't have to break a
sweat to kill this old fart.
I'll spare him, but you have to leave.
Please, don't make this any harder, Sanji!
Just leave!
Don't force me to kill both of you!
Run away!
Not a chance!
You look even dumber at gunpoint, old man!
What kind of example do you think
you're setting for All the other cooks?
I don't need a lecture
from a brat like you!
Would you stop calling me names?
Quit treating me like a kid!
This is crazy!
Sanji wouldn't abandon Zeff, now would he?
Dean!
Point that gun at me!
Hey!
But what if you die?
Shut up!
Sanji, why you?
Someone's eager to die.
Lucky for you, I'd be
more than happy to oblige.
Allow me.
It would be my pleasure to beat
you to a bloody lifeless pulp.
Absolutely natural, Pearl! Surprise!
Sanji!
Why didn't you dodge that?
Because if I did, that rat over
there would pull the trigger on Zeff.
Why are you doing this?
Just leave the restaurant
peacefully and no one gets hurt.
Please!
This restaurant is that old man's life.
I've already taken everything
else that man holds dear.
His power.
His dreams.
So while I'm around,
I'm not gonna let anything
else get taken from him!
Behind you!
Sanji!
The Hell Blue!
Yeah, it's out there somewhere, and all
that's even awesomer than they say it is!
stop being a doofus
that's just a fairy tale
for seafaring cooks don't
get me wrong we've all
had our little fantasies
about it but you gotta
remember that it's just
a dream a dream well I'm
gonna find the all-blue
then we'll see who's
dreaming that's quite the
quest good luck all right
there little man tell
me do you even know what
kind of place the all-blue
is yeah I do I'm not
The all-blue is a place for
fish from all four seas, Lou.
There's fish from East Blue, the West
Blue, the North Blue, and the South Blue.
To cooks who have taken to the
sea, it's an irresistible paradise!
I'll find it!
Oh, yeah!
That place is a gold mine.
It's got fish and plants
from all over the world.
Any chef would jump at
the chance to cook there.
True.
The cooks I know would risk
life and limb to find it.
Yeah.
Well, if it were real.
You think a miracle sea like the
all-blue could actually exist?
Think about it, kid.
It's impossible.
I bet it's probably just a lie
told by some daydreaming cook.
Okay, enough with the silly stories.
Get out there and collect
some plates, Sanji.
Oh, man. What a waste.
They left behind plates and plates
full of this delicious crop.
This one's barely been touched.
It's pretty good stuff, too.
I thought they'd love it for sure.
If you ask me, the customers
these days are spoiled.
It's way gross to eat the
leftovers of strangers.
You should just let me
throw that stuff away.
That kind of talk proves you've got a
whole lot to learn, so listen up, Shorty.
If you choose life on the high
seas, you've got to be resourceful.
The ocean is a strange
and unpredictable place
where wasting food could
be a fatal mistake.
So why don't you have some, eh? No way!
Don't go, people!
Panicking won't help!
Pirates are here!
What?
Pirates?
That ship!
It's Redfoot Zap and the Cook Pirates!
They're back from the Grand Line!
I take it you're the infamous
pirate, Captain Redfoot Zeff.
So, what do you want?
Steal!
Steal everything!
Addison nails down!
Those bastards!
I refuse to die at the
hands of those animals.
Oh, look at this!
Hey, killer.
If you're not careful, you might
just put someone's eye out with that.
He got me.
Look, I'm bleeding.
Shut up.
You mongrels better stay away from me.
Sanji.
Stop it, you'll make them mad.
A bit young to have a death wish.
But that's no reason not to grab it.
All right, you jerks, if I'm dying here,
then I'm taking some of you with me!
Donkey!
Wow, good one.
Yeah, that was brutal.
I'm not gonna die.
Not here!
I've got to live so that
I can find the all blue!
He said the all blue!
Pretty ambitious!
That's a good one!
Captain, should we tell the
little tyke it doesn't exist?
He won't... Shut up!
I'm not going to draw my last
breath until I've seen the old blue.
Captain, I recommend we
withdraw immediately.
This storm is way bigger than expected.
All right, men, playtime's over.
Let's load up the treasure
and get out of here.
Ah!
Ah! Damn brat!
Captain!
Why'd he risk his life for one measly kid?
Oh, my God!
The Brat finally wakes up.
You're lucky to be alive, you know.
Yeah, thanks.
Moving isn't a good idea.
You're still pretty banged
up from the beating, Yutub.
What about the ships? Who knows?
It was a terrible storm.
our ships were most likely destroyed.
It seems we're the only survivors.
Washed ashore on a desolate rock?
without so much as a coconut
tree to give us food.
Sure, there are fish in the sea,
but the rock has been
curved by the waves in such
a manner that we wouldn't
be able to climb back up?
if we ever went down.
Sad, isn't it?
This is all your fault, old man!
I hope you die!
You can whine all you want.
It won't help.
If nobody comes, we'll just dry up and
become two more skeletons in the sea.
Skeletons?
Really?
That bag there, it's your share of it.
It's some of the food that washed up.
Should be about five days' worth.
It's not much, but it's
better than nothing.
If you ration it out, it'll last longer.
Or use your head when you eat.
Good thing we're both cooks.
Hey, wait!
Is that bag your share of the food?
You got way more than me, you fat old pig!
Of course I get more food.
I'm a grown man, so I need more
to survive than a runt like you.
You should be grateful that
I'm sharing any of it with you.
Don't expect any pity
from me, you little brat.
Bastard!
Get to the other side of this
rock and watch for ships.
Let me know as soon as you see one.
Until then, don't bother talking
to me or moving from your post.
That'll just waste energy.
We can't afford that.
Good luck.
Screw you, Gramps.
I'm not saying anything if I see a ship.
I'll be fine.
I have five whole days worth of food.
We'll definitely see a ship
or two before I run out.
I'm sure of it.
Just to be extra safe, I'll
divide it up for 20 days.
That's more than enough
time to get rescued.
I guess all I got to do
now is sit and wait easy.
I'll make it through this thing.
No problem
Didn't see a ship today
That's all right.
It'll only be a few more days
I don't want to die.
This is it.
One moldy piece of bread.
Oh, man, what a waste.
They left behind plates and plates
full of this delicious grub.
It's way gross to eat the
leftovers of strangers.
You should just let me
throw that stuff away.
So why don't you have some, eh?
No way!
My last piece of bread.
I wonder...
Is the geyser dead yet?
He's alive!
And he's still got food!
A lot of food!
So much!
There's so much left!
You've got to get that food!
It's not fair that he has so
much more than me besides.
This is all his fault
What are you doing here your brat are
you here because you saw a ship I?
I came over here to
steal your food, old man.
If you want to kill me for it, go ahead.
Soon enough, I'll starve so
it makes no difference to me.
Didn't I tell you not to come
over here unless you saw a ship?
Why?
You said it's full.
Strange, isn't it?
We have all this money, and
yet we're going to starve.
It's only treasure.
It's worthless.
Hey, what's going on here old man?
Where's your food?
You had to have eaten something!
Now where is it?
I'm talking to you!
Answer me!
What happened to your leg?
The food!
Did you give me all of the food you had?
I did.
And you had to have known that without
that leg, you'd never be a pirate again.
That's right.
You old fool!
Why'd you help me?
It doesn't make sense to
sacrifice so much for me!
So why?
Tell me!
Because for my entire life,
I've had the same dream as you.
Be all blue.
But your men said that it doesn't exist.
Of course it does.
Never mind them.
When the time comes.
Head to the Grand Line.
That's where the old blue is sure to be.
My days.
As a pirate are done.
But you have your whole life.
To find it.
Don't die now. Get up.
Come on old man.
Don't you dare give up.
I wonder how many men have lost
their lives cursing the ocean,
knowing that it will soon be their grave.
This isn't the first time I've been
hungry enough to look death in the eyes,
and my thoughts are the same each time.
It is always my deepest wish that there
be a restaurant in the middle of the sea.
A restaurant?
Yeah, I was thinking that if I
make it out of this mess alive,
I'd like to build a restaurant
as my final purpose in life.
Great!
And I'll even help you do it!
So don't die, okay?
A weak little brat like you
couldn't be much good for anything.
Then I'll become strong!
So, don't die!
Help!
The geezer needs help! Over here!
Please help!
Please, please help us!
Hey!
Over here! Help us! This way!
Please, please!
Over here! Over here!
Help! Help! This way!
That old coot.
He gave up his legs so that I could live.
There's no way to repay the old geezer for
his kindness unless I
risk my life for him!
Why?
Why are you standing, Sanji?
Stay down.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
It's a little too much like giving up.
Idiot!
I'll kill you!
Cue little brat.
Ha!
That is so very refined of you.
But this restaurant will be closing soon.
And it'll open again for business.
As a pirate ship.
No, don't!
Gino, shoot the old man!
What's it do?
No, don't, don't!
Battle of it!
In my mind That I knew would Leave me I
had to find my way To that place Before
someone could beat me The promised land
Was in my grasp And I wouldn't let go
My only dream
I won't stop
chasing it Until it comes true
But if the world ever
changes I call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you My memories won't
fade Waiting for that one true dream?